Finding aid to the Sophia Smith Collection zines collection SSC.MS.00434
Sophia Smith Collection
Sophia Smith Collection zines collection
1967-2017
1991-1999
Sophia Smith Collection
SSC.MS.00434
19 boxes (9.25 linear feet)
Self-published magazines created primarily by women and girls who share a strong feminist perspective. Topics include "third wave" feminism, lesbian relationships, erotica, African American experiences around gender, and fat liberation. The collection is comprised primarily of individual issues, mostly dating from the 1990s.
Scope and Contents
The Sophia Smith Collection zines collection consists of self-published small magazines (known as "zines") created primarily by women and girls who share a strong feminist perspective. Topics include "third wave" feminism, African American experiences around gender, lesbian relationships and erotica, and fat liberation.
The collection is comprised primarily of individual issues, although there are longer runs for some titles and multiple titles for some authors. Most of the zines date from the 1990s, some of which were used in the book, A Girl's Guide to Taking Over the World, edited by Karen Green and Tristan Taormino (NY: St. Martin's, 1997).
Related Material
Tinúviel Papers, 1988-2005
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donors for zines in this collection include Tristan Taormino (donations in 1999 and 2010), Tinúviel (2005), Jenna Freedman (2007, 2010), the Smith College Campus Center Zines Library (2008), Smith alumna Anne "Daisy" Rooks, Class of 1997 (2009), Phoebe Harris (2010), Jess Artigliere (2016), and Shannon Supple (2017, 2018).
Additional zines have been purchased for the collection by the curator of the Sophia Smith Collection.
Arrangement
Most of the zines in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title. A small amount of loose materials, at least some of it from Tinúviel, are located at the end of the collection, as are recent groups of multiple titles by single authors, including Ajuan Mance.
Feminism--United States--Literary collections; Lesbian feminism--United States--History; Teenage girls in popular culture; African American women; Little magazines; Women authors, American --20th century; Women--Sexual behavior--Literary collections; Young women--United States--Social life and customs; Young women--United States--Literary collections; Green, Karen and Tristan Taormino (eds.). A girl's guide to taking over the world: writings from the girl zine revolution--Sources; Self-published magazines; Periodicals; Underground press publications -- United States; Taormino, Tristan; Artigliere, Jess; Freedman, Jenna; Harris, Phoebe; Rooks, Anne; Supple, Shannon; Taormino, Tristan; Tinúviel, 1963-; Mance, Ajuan Maria; Taormino, Tristan; Taormino, Tristan; Artigliere, Jess; Freedman, Jenna; Harris, Phoebe; Rooks, Anne; Supple, Shannon
- Ablaze, #7undated; #10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abuse, #3, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Action Girl Guide, #1, Winter 1993-1994 (Box 1)
- Action Teen, undated (Box 1)
- Adventure Playground, #3, Spring 1997 (Box 1)
- Ain't Nothing like Fucking in Moonshine!, #10, Summer 1995 (Box 1)
- Alien, #7undated; #10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alien Girl, #2, Summer 1995; Winter 1995 (Box 1)
- A Little Pamphlet Feb 1996 (2 copies) (Box 1)
- All Hail Me, #11, undated (Box 1)
- Alright!, #4Summer 1994; # 5, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alternative to What?, #2, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amazine, undated (Box 1)
- Ampheta-Zine, #1, undated (Box 1)
- Amputate, undated (Box 1)
- An Asexual's First by Lauren Hamell, 2018; 2018-S-0015 (Box 19)
- Anhedonia, Spring 1995; Summer 1995 (Box 1)
- Annzine, #1Mar 1995; #2Sep 1995; #3Nov. 1995; #4Spring 1996; #5Fall 1996; #6, Jan 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Another Lofi Technology: Story, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Apegirl, #1, undated (Box 1)
- Aphrodite's Trousers Spring 1996; #2, undated (Box 1)
- April Fool's Day, #1undated (2 copies) (Box 1)
- Attitude Problem, #25, undated (Box 1)
- Backseat, #1, Jul 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ball-Buster, #2, Nov 1993 (Box 1)
- Bamboo Girl, #21995 (2 copies); #3circa 1995; #4circa 1995; #5, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
- Battle Dress: 3 Women in Black, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Ben is Dead, #23Spring 1994; #25, 1995 (Box 2)
- Beer Frame, #3Sep 1994; #4, Mar 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bee's Knees, #1, undated (Box 2)
- Behavior that has you Worried, #1, undated (Box 2)
- Bestiary, undated (Box 2)
- Between no longer and not yet, Or, Learning to think with Pain, May 1997 (Box 2)
- Big Miss Moviola Directory, #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bikini Kill: A Color and Activity Book, undated (Box 2)
- Bikini Kill: Girl Power, #2, undated (Box 2)
- Billy's Mitten, #9, undated (Box 2)
- Bitch, #24, 1989 (Box 2)
- Bitter Critter, #11996; #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Blah Blah Blah, #3, undated (Box 2)
- Blood Sisters, undated (Box 2)
- Blue Hole, #1, 1995 (Box 2)
- Blue Stocking, #1, Winter 1996 (Box 2)
- Bobby is Fred, #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Bobby ("Bobby said Girls can't Skate…"), undated (Box 2)
- Boji for the Mentally Ill, #3Sep 1994; #4, Winter/Spring 1995 (Box 2)
- Boris Thru the Donut, undated (2 copies) (Box 2)
- Bookstore Review: 37 People, Spring 1987 (Box 2)
- Boy-Wonder, #1, undated (Box 2)
- Brain Spa 'Zine, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Brat, #5, undated (Box 2)
- Brat Attack, #3, 1992 (Box 2)
- Bunnyhop, #71996; #81997; #9, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bunny Rabbit, #41994; #6, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Burn Collector undated; Summer 1995; #3undated; #4 (Box 2)
- Bust, #4Summer/Fall 1994; #5Winter/Spring 1995; #6Fall 1995 (2 copies); #7Spring/Summer 1996 (2 copies); #8Fall/Winter 1996; #9Spring/Summer 1997; #11Summer/Fall 1998; #16, Winter 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- Busy Bea's Bush, #3, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Butch Nor Femme by Lynne Monsoon, 2011-2016; 2018-S-0016 (Box 19)
- Buttercup Gold, #1, Summer 1996 (Box 3)
- Butterknife junior, undated (Box 3)
- Butt Raisin, #1, Sep 1992 (Box 3)
- Cake Walk Apr 1997 (3 copies) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Caper Times, #12, Mar. 1999 (Box 3)
- Catch of the Day Fall 1997; Spring 1998, Summer 1998 (5 copies) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Cats and Dogs Pschogenie 76, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Caught in Flux, #1Spring 1993; #5, Spring 1996 (Box 3)
- Cha Cha Charming, Winter 1998 (Box 3)
- Chatty Cathy, #1undated; #2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chemical Imbalance, #1, undated (Box 3)
- Chickfactor, #4Fall 1993; #5Winter 1994; #6Summer 1994; #7Fall 1994; #8Winter 1995; #9Summer 1995; #10Fall 1996-Winter 1997; #11, Spring 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Chimps, #1undated; #2undated (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Choozy Distribution May 1996 (2 copies), 1997 (Box 4)
- Chronic Stressors, Spring 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Chunklet 11, Summer/Fall 1996 (Box 4)
- Cinnamon Stick, #3, 1997 (Box 4)
- Circumspect, #4, 1995 (Box 4)
- Confessions of a Teenage Transsexual Whore issues 1-10, 2014; 2017-S-0042; Harwood-Jones, Markus "Star" (Box 19)
- Cometbus!, #37undated; #38, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cosloidian, #2, undated (Box 4)
- Crucial Variable, #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Crystal Blue Persuasion, #3, Summer 1996 (Box 4)
- Cunt-a-licious, undated (Box 4)
- Cupcake, #3, 1996 (Box 4)
- Danzine, #14, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dagger, #25, Summer 1999 (Box 4)
- Dead Eyes Magazine, #6undated; #7 (Box 4)
- Dead Possum, #1, undated (Box 4)
- Deepsix Superstition, #2, Summer 1991 (Box 4)
- De/create, #2, Jun 1994 (Box 4)
- Deneuve, #2, Apr 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Derelict Speedball, #1Summer 1992; #2, Spring 1993 (Box 4)
- Disarm, #2, 1996 (Box 4)
- Discombobulation, #11, 1993 (Box 4)
- Dissonant Accost, #11987; #31994; #6undated; #81995; #13 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Don't Even…#3undated; #4, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Don't Shoot, #131995; #14Summer 1995; Vol. 2, no. 1, Spring 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Don't Touch my Bikini, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Double Bill, #3, 1993 (Box 5)
- Dreaming of Amelia, #1, Autumn 1995 (Box 5)
- Dykatude, #3, Spring 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Dyke Tyke, #2, 1997-98 (Box 5)
- Easting: By Ford and Pills, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ecce Queer Vol. 1, #1, Fall 1991 (Box 5)
- Emily's, #5, 1993 (Box 5)
- Emotional Biscuit, #12, 1994 (Box 5)
- Empty Quarter, #1, May 1991 (Box 5)
- Engelbert Humperdinck, #2, 1993 (Box 5)
- Epson Energy, #1Apr 1999; #21999; #3 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Escargot, Autumn 1995; Spring 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Everything I Touch Turns to Shit and Garbage, #1, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Evil Twin, undated (Box 5)
- Fantastic Fanzine 3.5, undated (Box 5)
- Fat Boy Fan Club, #14Summer 1995; #15, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Fat Girl, #21995; #5 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- FBIO, May 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Femme Flicke Jul 1996; #2circa 1996; #3undated (2 copies); #4undated; #51996; #6circa 1996-1997 (2 copies); #7 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
- Fierce Femme, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- File 13, #15Spring 1993; #16, Summer 1993 (Box 6)
- Fishin' Buddies, #1, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Five Dollar Walk, 1994 (Box 6)
- Fix Me, undated (Box 6)
- Flatter!, #51994; #71996; #81996; #9, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Flim Flam Summer 1996; #2, Winter 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Flower Bridge, #1, Spring 1997-98 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Flypaper, #4, undated (Box 6)
- For Paper Airplane Pilots, #5, May 1995 (Box 6)
- Foxy Digitalis, #2, Apr 1996 (Box 6)
- Frank's Depression, 1992 (Box 6)
- From Nods to Nothing, 1996 (Box 6)
- Gap Tooth Bitches #1, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Get Hit Smashed Smacked Punched the Whole Way Home, undated (Box 6)
- Ghoul Girl, #1, 1996 (Box 6)
- Gingerboy, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Ginger's Hut, Jan 1995 (Box 6)
- Girl Band Guide, #7, Nov 1993 (Box 6)
- Girl Cola, #4, Dec 1992 (Box 6)
- Girl Con, 1997 (Box 6)
- Girl Frenzy, #3undated; #4Aug 1993; #5undated; #6undated; Millennial, Nov 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
- Girlie Jones volume 1, issue 4 "Sex Issue: So Much Fun it Makes Us Scream", 1995 September/October; 2018-S-0019 (Box 19)
- G irlfriends, May/Jun 1995; Aug 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Girl Germs undated; #3undated; #5 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Girl Hero, #2, Feb 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Girlie Jones, Vol. 1, #3, Aug 1995 (Box 6)
- Girl Jock, #10, 1993 (Box 6)
- Girl Power!, undated (Box 6)
- Glue, #2, Aug 1992 (Box 6)
- Goddess Violated, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Good Faerie, #7, undated (Box 7)
- Googlebox, #4Winter 1995 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Go Metric, #4, Winter 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Gorgeous, Dec 1996 (Box 7)
- Graham Cracker Cereal, #11994-95; #2, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Grit, #3, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Ha!, #2, Spring 1998 (Box 7)
- Hands Off XOXO, undated (Box 7)
- Hayfever, #1, Apr 1995 (Box 7)
- Head Shaved Smooth, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Heavens to Betsy, undated (Box 7)
- I Love You, Hello Kitty!, undated (Box 7)
- Hessian Obsession, #2, undated (Box 7)
- Hey Girl!, #2, Spring 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Hey Girlfriend, undated (Box 7)
- Hey There, Barbie Girl!, #4, undated (Box 7)
- Hip Mama, #9, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Hit It of Quit It, #8, Fall 1996 (Box 7)
- Honeysuckle, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Housewears, undated (Box 7)
- Hungaro, #2, 1992 (Box 7)
- Hursay, 1994 (Box 7)
- HX for Her, #099, 27 Nov 1998 (Box 7)
- Hyacinth, May 1993; Autumn 1993; 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Hysteria, #8, Spring 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Ice Cream and Cheese Vol. 1, #2, Nov 1993 (Box 7)
- Ideas in Pictures, #4, undated; 2018-S-0025 (Box 19)
- I Love Amy Carter, #4, Jan 1994 (Box 7)
- I Kicked a Boy!, #4, undated (Box 7)
- Imaginary Friend, #3, Apr 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- I miss you all!, Sep 1994 (Box 7)
- I'm Muscle not Bones, undated (Box 7)
- I'm Not Shy…I Just Hate People, #31995; #4, May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- I'm Not Waiting, 1997 (Box 7)
- Incite!, #26Autumn 1994; #27Summer 1995; #28Feb 1996; #29, May 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Independent Catalogue, #2, Mar 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Indignant Gingham, #1, Mar 1995 (Box 7)
- Inkling, #11993-1994; #2, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- International Hipster, #1, Summer 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Interrobang?!, #3, Winter 1996-97 (Box 8)
- Introductory Mechanic's Guide undated (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Isollae, #1, undated (Box 8)
- Jailhouse Turnout, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Jen, #1, 1993 (Box 8)
- Jigsaw, #5.5, 1994 (Box 8)
- Jing Bang, #4, May 1994 (Box 8)
- Joe Preston's Legs A.K.A 'Germ of Youth', #1undated; #2Summer 1992; #3Oct. 1992; #4, Winter 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- K, #28, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Kali Yantra, 1998 (Box 8)
- Kappa King, #1, 1992 (Box 8)
- Kelp, #5, Summer 1995 (Box 8)
- Kitty Magik, #1Fall 1997; #2Summer/Fall 1998; #3Summer/Fall 1999; #4Winter 2000; #5, Summer 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
- Kill Rock Stars, Winter 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Kill the Robot, #6, undated (Box 8)
- Kissing Girls Coloring Book by Karen Llamas, 2017; Llamas, Karen Kaye (Box 8)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Shannon Supple, 2018.
- Krash Karp!, #4, undated (Box 8)
- Kusp, #1, Summer 1995 (Box 8)
- Kutie, #21998; #3undated; #4undated; #5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Ladies Art Revival, Spring 1998; Fall 1998; 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Last Meanderings, #1, Nov 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Kissing (Box 8)
  This item was donated by Shannon Supple and is part of accession 2018-S-0010
- LA Weekly, undated (Box 8)
- Lezzie Smut Vol. 1, #1Sep 1993; Vol. 1, #3, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Libel, #15, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Liberation Through Hearing, Spring 2001 (Box 8)
- Lighter Shade of Peroxide May 1995; #9undated; #11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Lipstick my Espionage, #2, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Lofi is Forever, undated (Box 9)
- Love and Rockets, #501996 (a folder of materials) (Box 9)
- Lowest Common Denominator, #18, Summer 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Lucid Nation, #1, 1995 (Box 9)
- Lusy's Angry, #2, undated (Box 9)
- Madeline, #1, Fall 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Mail Libel, 1993 (Box 9)
- Make Your Own Fun by Kristyna Baczynski, 2016; 2018-S-0017 (Box 19)
- Mary had a Mammogram, #8, undated (Box 9)
- Marika, undated (Box 9)
- Más Amor, Por Favor, Mujeristas Collective, circa 2018; 2018-S-0070; Mujeristas Collective; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
- Maximumbo, #105Feb 1992; #109Jun 1992; #122, Jul 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Maximum Rock-n-Roll, #129Feb. 1994; #130, Mar 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Maxine, #11995; #2, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Meat Cake circa 2000 (6 copies); #4, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Miau!, #5, Aug 1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Milk-Toast, #2, 1993 (Box 9)
- Mimi's Revenge, #1, Summer 1995/Winter 1996 (Box 9)
- Minus Times, #211997; #23circa 1998; #24 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Miss Love, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Miss Mary Mack undated; #4, 1994 (Box 9)
- Missoula City Massacre Presents: Needlenosepliers, undated (Box 9)
- Mohawk Beaver, #31997; #41998 (2 copies); #5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Molasses Soulkiss, #2, 1993 (Box 9)
- Mommy and I are One undated; #2Spring 1995; #3undated; #4, Summer/Fall 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Mona, #1, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Monster, #2, undated (Box 10)
- Mouthful of Monkey Bile, undated (Box 10)
- Moxie, 1997 (Box 10)
- Mr. Lady Records and Videos, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Mucho Coolan' Manifesto, undated (Box 10)
- Muffin Boones, #10, Summer/Fall 1995 (Box 10)
- Murder can be Fun, #11, undated (Box 10)
- My Brightest Summer, #2undated; #3undated; #4undated; #5.1, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- My Evil Twin Sister, #2, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- My Life and My Sex Thrive in the J.Crew Catalogue, #2, 1994 (Box 10)
- My Life with Evan Dando, Popstar, undated (Box 10)
- Mylxine, #9undated; #10 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- My New Gun, #11995; #2undated; #3, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Naughty Bits, #9, Jun 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Navigating the Space Between Brilliance and Madness, undated (Box 10)
- Neo-Psychedelic Man, #16, Jan. 1993 (Box 10)
- Neptunes Bride, #2, Nov. 1993 (Box 10)
- Nerd Girl, #1undated; #2c. 1994; #3c. 1994; #4 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- New School News Vol. 4, no. 15, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Ninja Fanzine: Silent Death, #2, undated (Box 10)
- No Room for Squares, #31995; #5, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- No Spikes, No Chains, #1, Feb 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Notes Zine, #11undated (2 copies) (Box 10)
- Not Just Another Cookbook, #1, 1994 (Box 10)
- Not Sisters Feb 1996 (2 copies) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Nuthing Sacred, #6, Spring 1993 (Box 10)
- Ocho y Media, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Of all the Beautiful Women in the World, undated (Box 11)
- Oh Boy…, #1, 1997 (Box 11)
- OkStupid: a Zine about Online Dating, Julia Emiliani, 2016; 2018-S-0018 (Box 19)
- On Our Backs, Jul/Aug. 1994; Sep/Oct 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Orifice, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Origami Disaster, #6, undated (Box 11)
- Origami IAP, Jan. 1996 (Box 11)
- Outpunk, #4June 1995; #5Spring 1996; #6 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Pacifier, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Panacea, #1Winter 1996; #3undated; #4, Spring 1997 (Box 11)
- Pandora's Box, #2, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Panegyric, #2, 1995 (Box 11)
- Panophobia, #2Winter 1993/1994; #31994; #4, Spring 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Paper, Scissors, Clocks, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Parlez-vous Code Fucker, 1993 (Box 11)
- Paste, #1, Summer 1997 (Box 11)
- Patrice is the president of RISE, undated (Box 11)
- Pawholes, #4undated; #51995 (2 copies); #6, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Pea Soup, #2, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Pee Chees, undated (Box 11)
- Pigs and Pedagouges, 1993 (Box 11)
- Pippiletta, undated (Box 11)
- Platinum, Vol. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Plushtoy Catalog, 1997-98 (Box 11)
- Plushtoy Picture Book, 1993 (Box 11)
- Poemfishgrrl, #11998; #5, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Polly Gets Off, 1996 (Box 11)
- Pook, #31993; #4undated; #5 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Popnausea, #2, 1995 (Box 11)
- Popwatch, #41993 (2 copies); #5Spring 1994; #6Winter 1994; #71995; #8Winter/Spring 1997 (2 copies); #9Spring/Summer 1998; #10, Winter/Spring 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
- Pout, #4, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Prettier Alone, undated (Box 12)
- Princess, #1Spring 1995 (2 copies) (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Printed Matter Catalog, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Psycho Genic!!, #18undated; #33 (Box 12)
- Puberty Strike, 1997 (Box 12)
- Pucker Up, Vol. 1, no. 4, Fall/Winter 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Puddle Jumper, Weather Stomper, #3, 1994 (Box 12)
- Puffy Fruit, 1999 (Box 12)
- Pulp, #7, 1992 (Box 12)
- Punk in my Vitamins?, #3Summer 1993; #2, Jan 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Punk Life, #15, 1994 (Box 12)
- Punk Planet, #8Jul/Aug 1995; #12Mar/Apr 1996; #15Oct/Nov 1996; #17Mar/Apr 1997; #18May/Jun 1997; #241998; #27Sep/Oct 1998; #28, Nov/Dec 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
- Punk Rock Word Finds, #1, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Pure Vamp, 1992; undated (Box 13)
- Pussy Cat!, #4, Fall 1995 (Box 13)
- Quagmire, #1, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Quarter Inch Squares, #4, 1995 (Box 13)
- Queen Bee Reader, #1, undated (Box 13)
- The Queers, Jenny Lin, 2015; 2018-S-0066; Lin, Jenny; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
  Zines
- Quimby, #1, undated (Box 13)
- Racecar Sporadical, #102, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Ragweed, #3, 1994 (Box 13)
- Ramble Right, undated (Box 13)
- Ramea City USA, #2, Winter 1993 (Box 13)
- Rats Live on No Evil StarTrona!, #6, 1996 (Box 13)
- Real-Tuff, #1, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Red Pop Revenge, #3, Spring 1995 (Box 13)
- Reggae Chicken, undated (Box 13)
- Resist, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Resister Vol. 1, no. 1Winter 1996; Vol. 1, no. 2, Fall/Winter 1996 (Box 13)
- Revolution Calling, #6, Jan 1997 (Box 13)
- Revolution Rising, #5, Summer 1995 (Box 13)
- Riot Grrr undated; Feb 1992; #2Mar 1992; #3May 1992; #7undated (2 different editions); undated (3 copies); circa 1993, single page (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Riot Gear, #3, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Robot Power, #20.5, undated (Box 14)
- Rock for Choice, undated (Box 14)
- Rock Hardi News, #23.3, Oct 1993 (Box 14)
- Rockrgrl Issue #37 - Issue #57, Jan/Feb 2001 - Fall 2005 (Box 14A, Folder 1-5)
- Rockrgrl Vol. 1, Issue #1 - Issue #36, Jan/Feb 1995 - Nov/Dec 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3-8)
- Rock Vibe, Apr 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Rocktober, #12Winter 1995; #14, Halloween 1995 (Box 15)
- Roller Derby, #4Winter 1991; #111993; #12July 1993; #17Summer 1995; #181996; "Generation L", undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Roller Grrrl Kills, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Ron Rege Jr. stories, 1999; 2000 (Box 15)
- Ruby Falls and Rodan Tour 1994 Coloring Book (Box 15)
- Runt, #221994 (2 copies), #24undated (CD enclosed) (split issue with Yakuza, #7) (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Sally Tomato, #2Spring 1996; #3, Winter 1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Sappho's Scribblers, #2, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Scarifications, 1973 (Box 15)
- Scent: The Zine, undated (Box 15)
- Scheme of Things, undated (Box 15)
- Scout's Handbook, #12, Jan. 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Scram, #1, Summer 1992 (Box 15)
- Screams from Inside, #7, undated (Box 15)
- SCUM Manifesto (excerpts), 1967 (Box 15)
- Secret Agent Girl no. 666, #11998; #2undated; #4, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Secret Politics of Providence Vol. 1, Fall 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Septophilia Mailorder, #2.5, Fall 1994 (Box 15)
- Self-Defense, #3, 1997 (Box 15)
- Sew, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Sex Panic, 1997 (Box 15)
- Sexism, undated (Box 15)
- Share the Modern World with Me! Vol. 1, #2, Fall 1992 (Box 15)
- Shark Week by Janice Quiles-Reyes, 2017; 2018-S-0010; Quiles-Reyes, Janice (Box 15)
  This zine was donated to the collection by Shannon Supple in 2018.
- Sharp Shooter, undated (Box 15)
- Show Me the Money, 2004-2005; 2018-S-0025 (Box 19)
- Skew, #1undated; #2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Slander Zine, #5, Apr/Jun 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Slurs in Context, #1, undated (Box 15)
- Smart Ass, #3, 1995 (Box 15)
- Snakers, Eloisa Aquino and Jenny Lin, 2018; 2018-S-0067; Lin, Jenny; Aquino, Eliosa; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
- Sneer, #5, Spring 1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Soft Smooth Brain, undated (Box 15)
- Some Hope and Some Despair, #1, 1996 (Box 15)
- Someone Loves me in Ohio, #2, 1996 (Box 15)
- Sourpuss, #7undated; #8undated; #9c. 1996; #10 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Sparkly Kitty Stickers, #5, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Speed Kills, #51993; #7Sep 1995 (vinyl disc enclosed) (Box 16)
- Splashdown, #3Fall 1994; #4, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Starlite and Crazed, #1undated; #2, 1997 (Box 16)
- Starring…'The Menstral Mamers', undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Stay Free!, Spring 1997 (Box 16)
- Stifled, #6, undated (Box 16)
- Strange Fruit, #1, Autumn 1995 (Box 16)
- Structure, Aug 1994 (Box 16)
- Surefire Distributors, Dec 1995 (Box 16)
- Tales of Blarg, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Tally, #7, undated (Box 16)
- Tamper Evident, #1, 1998 (Box 16)
- Tazewell's Favorite Eccentric, undated (Box 16)
- Tear Down the Sky, #12, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Teenage Gang Debs, #5, May 1993 (Box 16)
- Teen Fag, undated (Box 16)
- Tesseracting, Megan Bentley, 2011; 2018-S-0020 (Box 19)
- That Girl Zine, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Thecounterfeit, undated (Box 16)
- These Tools my Fingerprints, undated (Box 16)
- This Armadillo has Leprosy, 1991 (Box 16)
- This is one Friend you'd Sell, #3, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- This Little Girl…, undated (Box 16)
- Thrift Score, #8, 1996 (Box 16)
- Thrill!, #13, undated (Box 16)
- Throbbing Gristle, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Tickertape and the Staple Museum, #1, undated (Box 16)
- Tobis' Veil, #2, 1996 (Box 16)
- Too Far, #11, undated (Box 16)
- Topsy Turvy Twister Rama, #1, 1983 (Box 16)
- Toward a Psychology of Being, #21995 (2 copies) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Trailer Trash, #8, Jan 1997 (Box 16)
- Trellisaze Pixie, 1995 (Box 16)
- Tuba Frenzy, #2, Summer/Fall 1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Turkish Delight, undated (Box 16)
- TVI, #2, undated (Box 16)
- Twat!, #2Jun 1996 (2 copies) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Twelve, #4undated; #5undated; #6, 1993 (Box 17)
- Twelve Thousand Words, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Twenty Bus, 1995 (Box 17)
- Twisted Sister, #4, 1994 (Box 17)
- Two Clowns Fucking Around, #1, May 1996 (Box 17)